Guide to the Records of the Asian/Pacific/American Institute RG.21.35
New York University Archives
- Series II: Administrative, 504
  - Subseries A: Sheelagh Cabalda, Office for African American, Latino and Asian American Student Services (OASIS), 162374
    - Tony Formerito, 2000; 162585 (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Tseng/May Immigrant Study "Enhancing Educational Experiences at NYU: A Report on Immigration", 2000; 162586 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - TSOA Student Affairs, 1997-1998; 162587 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - UConn Storrs Conference, 2002; 162588 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Under One Roof, 1997-1998; 162589 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - UVA Conference, 2004; 162591 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Washington Square News, 1995; 162592 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Witness Tree - Dr. Rosaking, 2000; 162593 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - World AIDS Day, 1995-1996; 162594 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Working Retreat, 2003; 162595 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - WSN Coverage, 1996-1997; 162596 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Youth Community Groups, 2000; 162597 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Subseries B: Tomio Geron, Academic Program Coordinator Asian/Pacific/American Studies Program, 613
    Subseries B contains correspondence, memoranda, and reports related to the further development of the A/P/A studies academic program. This includes new course proposals, staff and faculty job descriptions, the development of a mission statement, departmental magazines, and the creation of an alumni association. These records reflect the planning involved in the ongoing development of the academic program.
    - Alumni Association, 1997; 670 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Area/Ethnic Studies, 1998; 669 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Artist Programs, 1998; 668 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Asian American Media Archives, 2000; 667 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Asian American Related Video Collections, 1997; 666 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Asian Council and EQUAL Commission, 1994; 665 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Asian Pacific American Studies: Major Development, 1998; 664 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Asian Pacific American Studies: Minor Program Proposal, 1997-1998; 663 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Asian Pacific American Studies: Program Meeting, 1997; 662 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Asian Pacific American Studies: Retreat Agenda, 1996; 661 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Asian Pacific American Studies: Scripts, circa 1999; 660 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Asians in America Conference, 1997; 659 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Asians in America Conference, 1998; 658 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Campomanes, Oscar, 1997; 657 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Challenge Fund Grant Application, 1998; 656 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Chinese Construction Workers at NYU, 1997-1998; 655 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1996-1997; 654 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1997; 653 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence (incoming and outgoing): Dean Santirocco, 1999; 652 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Co-Sponsorship, 1997; 651 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Co-Sponsorship, 1997; 650 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Course Descriptions, 1997-1998; 649 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Course Proposal, 1997; 647 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1997; 646 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Curriculum Plan, 1997; 645 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Directors Undergraduate Study Meeting Schedule, 1997; 644 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - East of California Network, 1997; 643 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Events, 1997; 642 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Faculty Correspondence, 1996-1997; 641 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Follow Up Items, 1998; 640 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Internal Sessions, 1996; 639 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - International Visitors Program, 1997-1998; 638 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Mission Guidelines, 1996-1997; 637 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - NYU in Hong Kong, 1999; 181413 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Office Renovations: General, 1997; 636 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Office Renovations: Furniture, 1997; 635 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Pan-a-Visions Newsletter: Meeting, 1998; 634 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Pan-A-Visions Newsletter: Overview, circa 1998; 633 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Petitions, circa 1998; 632 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Personnel Meeting Agenda, 1996; 631 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Post-doctoral Fellow Paper Proposal, 1997; 630 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Program Coordinator Position, 1998; 629 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Public Events, 1996; 628 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Public Programming: Maya Lin, 1998; 627 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Publicity, 1995-1996; 626 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Reports and Memos: General, 1997-1998; 625 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Research, circa 1997; 624 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Research Assistant Job Description, 1996; 623 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Staff Meeting Notes, 1997-1998; 622 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Student Coordinators, 1996-1997; 621 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Student Surveys, 1996; 620 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Student Surveys, 1996; 619 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Working Session: Colonialism, Diaspora, and the Americas, 1997; 618 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Working Session: Community Documentation, 1997; 617 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Working Session: Community Studies and Curriculum, 1997; 616 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Working Session: Curriculum, 1997; 615 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Working Session: South Asian American Studies, 1996-1997; 614 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Subseries C: Risa Morimoto, Administrator and Asian/Pacific/American Institute Coordinator, 505
    Subseries C includes general course information related to the A/P/A program in addition to various events sponsored by the department. This subseries contains syllabi, course evaluations, course proposals and event records.
    - Asian Artists, 181423 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Asian Arts Organizations, 181424 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Artist-in-Residence: General, Undated, 1996; 612 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Artist-in-Residence: Jessica Hagedorn, 1998-1999; 611 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Artists Series, 1999; 610 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Asian Pacific American Archives and Media Center, 1999-2000; 609 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Asian Pacific American Book Collection, 1998; 608 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Asian Pacific American Studies Minor, 1997; 607 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Asians in America Conference, 1996-1997; 606 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Audre Lorde Project, 1998; 603 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Budget Proposal, 1997-1998; 602 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Budget Proposal, 1998-2000; 601 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Cantonese I Course: Planning, 1999; 600 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Cantonese II Course: Approval Form, 1999; 599 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Challenge Fund Grant, 1997; 598 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Community Documentation and Census 2000, 1997; 597 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1997-1998; 596 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Co-Sponsorships, 1999; 595 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Course Proposals, 1997-1998; 591 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Course Proposals, 1999-2000; 590 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Courses, 1996-1997; 589 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Curriculum Planning, 1999-2000; 588 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Development: Notes, 1998; 587 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Development Correspondence: General, 1997-1999; 586 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Development Correspondence: American Express, 1999-2000; 585 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Development Correspondence: Anheuser-Busch, 1999; 584 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Development Correspondence (outgoing): Anna Sui, 1999; 583 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Development Correspondence: Bell Atlantic, 1999; 582 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Development Correspondence: Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation, 1999; 581 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Development Correspondence: Rockefeller Foundation, 181143 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Development Correspondence: Carnegie Corporation of New York, 1999-2000; 580 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Development Correspondence: Lucent Technologies, 2000; 579 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Development Correspondence: Starr Foundation, 1998; 578 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Development Correspondence (outgoing): Vivienne Tam, 1999; 577 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Development Correspondence (outgoing): Yahoo, 1999; 576 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - East of California Conference, 1997; 575 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - East of California Conference, 1997; 574 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - East of California Conference, 1997; 573 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - East of California Conference, 1997; 572 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - East of California Conference, 1997; 571 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - East of California Conference, 1997; 570 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - East of California Conference, 1997; 569 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - End of the Year Party Logistics, 1998; 566 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Event: Dangerous Music, Fierce Women, 1998; 565 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Event: "Maya Lin: Topologies", 1998; 564 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Event Planning, 1998-1999; 563 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Fall Courses: Listings, 1997; 561 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Fall Courses: Listings, 1998; 560 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Fall Courses: Listings, 1999; 559 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Fall Course Listings, 2004; 169254 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Fall Courses: Proposals, 1997; 558 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Fall Courses: Proposals, 1998; 181447 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Faculty, 181414 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Faculty-Recruitment and Search, 181415 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Faculty-Affiliated and Adjunct, 181416 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Intermediate Tagalog II Course Proposal, 1999; 556 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Interoffice Memoranda, 1996; 555 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Jan Lo Shinebourne Reception, 1997; 554 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - JANM Talk, 1998; 553 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - JANM/Jewish Talk, 1997-1998; 552 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - JANM Workshops, 1999; 551 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Keep Event, 1997; 550 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Kelly Loves Tony Film Screening, 1998; 549 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Kerri Sakamoto Reading, 1999; 548 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Letters to Thien Film Screening, 1999; 547 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Life After NYU Series, 1997; 546 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - NYU Departmental Events, 1997-1999; 545 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - NYU Publications, 1996-1997; 544 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Open House, 1997; 543 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Open House, 1997; 542 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Opening of A/P/A Studies Program and Institute, 1997; 541 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Program Budget, 1997; 539 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Proposed Courses, 1996; 538 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Publicity, 1997; 537 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Sino-American Training Project, 1998; 535 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Small Events and Co-Sponsorships, 1998-1999; 534 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - South Asia Pilot, 1998; 533 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Spring Courses: Proposals, 1997; 532 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Spring Reception, 1998; 529 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Spring Syllabi, 1999; 528 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Summer Course Listings, 2000; 527 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Syllabus: Cinema of Asia-America, 1998; 526 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Syllabus: Conversational Tagalog I, 1998-1999; 525 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Syllabus: Filming Asia America, Documenting Community, 1999; 524 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Syllabus: Media and Culture, 1999; 523 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Syllabus: Reading Race and Representation, 181448 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Tomie Arai Exhibit Opening Reception, 1998; 521 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Visiting Faculty Program, 1998; 520 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Visiting Scholars: General, 1999; 519 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Visiting Scholar: Anju Bhargava, 1998; 517 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Visiting Scholar: Doris Lee, 1998; 512 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Visiting Scholar: Fabiana Chin, 1997; 516 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Visiting Scholar: Gloria Lee, 1998; 511 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Visiting Scholar: Grace Hong, 1998; 515 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Visiting Scholar: Margo Machida, 1997; 509 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Visiting Scholar: Mimi Young, 1998; 507 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Visiting Scholar: Sonny Ago, 1997-1999; 518 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Visiting Scholar: Sunaina Maira, 1996; 508 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Visiting Scholar: Tan A. Lin, 1998; 510 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Visiting Scholar: Tarry Hum, 1998; 514 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Visiting Scholar: Tineke Jansen, 1998-1999; 513 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Working Sessions, 1997; 506 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Subseries D: Syllabi, 221943
    Subseries D contains syllabi from classes given at A/P/A.
    - Syllabi -- Spring, 1998; 221944 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Syllabi -- Fall, 1998; 221945 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Syllabi -- Spring, 1999; 221946 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Syllabi -- Fall, 1999; 221947 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Syllabi -- Spring, 2000; 221948 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Syllabi -- Fall, 2000; 221949 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Syllabi -- Spring, 2001; 221950 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Syllabi -- Fall, 2001; 221951 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Series III: Events, 1995-2003; 379
  Series III consists of information regarding various events and activities produced and sponsored by the A/P/A Institute. These records are primarily comprised of outreach materials, such as posters, brochures, and flyers. The majority of these events are art-related, such as gallery exhibitions, author reading series, and film screenings. Events also include lectures and discussions regarding various issues relevant to the A/P/A student community. Many of these events were documented either on film or audio. These recordings are included in the collection. This series is divided into three subseries: a series of general materials organized alphabetically, a series of posters, and a series of general materials organized chronologically. The material in Subseries 3 was received at a later date, and its chronological organization has been retained.
  - Subseries A: General (Alphabetical), 789
    - A. 100 Gala, 169263 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - A Gathering of Tribes, 2003-2004; 181417 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Alumni Gallery Viewing, 2002; 856 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Annual Holiday Party, 1999; 425 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Annual Holiday Party, 2001; 460 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - Annual Holiday Party, 2002; 501 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - Annual Holiday Party-Silent Auction, 2006; 181155 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - Art Catalogs, 2002-2012; 222140 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Artist in Residence, 1 of 2, 1998-2012; 222141 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Artist in Residence, 2 of 2, 1999-2012; 222142 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Artist in Residence: David Henry Hwang, 2000; 500 (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - Artist in Residence: Jessica Hagedorn, 1998; 499 (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - Artist in Residence: Ping Chong, 1999; 437 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - Artist Talk: Corky Lee, 2002; 498 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - Artist Talk: Corky Lee: Asian Americans and the Vietnam War, 2003; 400 (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - Artist Talk: Serene Ford Northington, 2003; 403 (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - Artist Talk: Mary Ting, 2002; 497 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - Artist: Dana Tai Soon Burgess and Company, 2001-2002; 181156 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Artist: Wen Ho Lee, 2002; 181157 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Artist: Vijai Nathan, 2001; 181158 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Artist: Susan Sponsler, 2000; 181159 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Artist: Flo Oy Wong, undated; 181160 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Asian Pacific American Heritage Month, 1999; 169264 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Asian Pacific American Youth Identity Forum: Building Bridges, 1999; 488 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Asian Pacific American Youth Identity Forum: Exploring the Unseen and Unspoken, 2000; 463 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Asian Pacific American Youth Identity Forum: Freezone, 2000; 459 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Asian Pacific American Youth Identity Forum: Pursuit of Pop, 2001; 433 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Asian Pacific American Youth Identity Forum: Urbanizasian, 2002; 858 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Asians in America Conference, 1995; 495 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Asians in America Conference, 1995; 184270 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Asians in America Conference, 1995; 184271 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Asians in America Conference, 1995; 494 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Asians in America Conference, 1995; 493 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Asians in America Conference, 1995; 492 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Asians in America Conference, 1996; 181161 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Asians in America Conference, 1997; 181162 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Asians in America Conference, 1998; 181163 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Asians in America Conference, 1999; 181164 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Asians in America Conference Proceedings, 1 of 2, 1995; 222143 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Asians in America Conference Proceedings, 2 of 2, 1995; 222144 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Asian Americans in the Arts, undated; 181165 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Asian Americans in the Arts, undated; 181166 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Benefit Reading for Premonitions: The Kaya Anthology of New Asian North American Poetry, 2000; 490 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Breaking Stereotypes: Asian Pacific American Musicians, 2003; 396 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Brown Bag Lunch Series: Gary Okihiro On the Death of Ethnic Studies, 2003; 392 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Brown Bag Lunch Series: May Joseph, Migrancy, Citizenship and New York City, 2003; 398 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Brown Bag Lunch Series: Reclaiming Lives with Ruthanne Lum McCunn, 1997; 430 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Brown Bag Lunch Series: Re-visioning the City, 2003; 402 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Chang-Rae Lee Reading A Gesture Life, 2000; 484 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Civil Rights Issues and Post 9-11 Law Enforcement/Community Relations in New York: A Fact Finding Forum, 2003; 390 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Coming of Age in Amelika, 2001; 483 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Coming to Terms: The Impact of WWII on American Jews and Japanese Americans Today, 1998; 482 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Commencement and Alumni Receptions, 2003; 391 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Course Offerings, 1997-1998; 222120 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Course Offerings, 1998; 481 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Course Offerings, 1999; 480 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Course Offerings, 2000; 479 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Course Offerings, 2000; 478 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Course Offerings, 2000-2005; 222121 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Course Offerings, 2001; 477 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Dilemmas of Historical Memory: Locating South Asian Americans in Asian America Lecture, 1997; 474 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Dog Eat Dog Party with Jessica Hagedorn, 1999; 473 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Dogeaters: Conversation with Jessica Hagedorn, 2001; 472 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - East of California Conference, 1997; 471 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - East of California Conference, 1997; 181168 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - East of California Conference-President's Dinner, 1997; 181169 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Educator's Institute on Asian Americans, 181418 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Emerging Artists Series: Le Thi Diem Thuy, 1999; 469 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Emerging Artists Series: Staceyann Chin, "I was Born with Two Tongues", 1999; 468 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Emerging Artists Series: Suheir Hammad, 2001; 467 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Emerging Artists Series: Vijay Iyer, 2000; 466 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Empire of Care Book Launch with Catherine Ceniza Choy, 2003; 395 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Ephemera, 1 of 8, 1999-2007; 222145 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Ephemera, 2 of 8, 1999-2011; 222146 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Ephemera, 3 of 8, 1998-2013; 222147 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Ephemera, 4 of 8, 2002-2012; 222148 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Ephemera, 5 of 8, 2001-2011; 222149 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Ephemera, 6 of 8, 1999-2011; 222150 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Ephemera, 7 of 8, 1997-2012; 222151 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Ephemera, 8 of 8, 1999-2011; 222152 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Ephemera -- Emergences and Emergencies, New South Asian Film Making from Britain, 2007; 222153 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Events Calendar and Pan-A-Visions (A/P/A Studies Newsletter), 1998; 464 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Events Calendar, 2000-2001; 465 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Events Calendar, 2002; 486 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Events Calendar, 2002; 487 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Events Calendar, 2003; 389 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Events Calendar, 2003; 405 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Events Calendar, 2004-2006; 222154 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Events Calendar, 2005; 181170 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Events Calendar, 2007-2009; 222155 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Events Calendar, 2010-2012; 222156 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Film Screening: Global Village or Global Pillage, 1997-1999; 181171 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Film Screening: Kelly Loves Tony, 1998; 181172 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Film Screening: Korean Film Festival, 2000; 181173 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Film Screening: The Game of Their Lives, 2003; 401 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Film Screening: Raising Our Voices, 2002; 431 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Film Screening: Say I Do, 2003; 426 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Film Screening: An Untold Triumph, 2003; 397 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Films: Activist Media, undated; 181175 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Flower Drum Song Symposium, 2002; 461 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Flower Drum Song Press and Release Forms, undated; 181174 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Forums, Symposiums and Conferences, 1 of 6, 1997-2012; 222157 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Forums, Symposiums and Conferences, 2 of 6, 1998-2006; 222158 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Forums, Symposiums and Conferences, 3 of 6, 1998-2001; 222159 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Forums, Symposiums and Conferences, 5 of 6, 1996-2012; 222160 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Forums, Symposiums and Conferences, 6 of 6, 2000-2003; 222161 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Garden of Export Delights with Swati Khurana, 2000; 458 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Gender, Cultural Citizenship and Transnationalism, 2002; 457 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Gender, Cultural Citizenship and Transnationalism, 2002; 456 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - General APA Information, Undated; 222162 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Helen Zia: Asian American Dreams Book Reception, 2000; 455 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - I of Beholder Exhibition, 2000; 454 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Illiterate Heart by Meena Alexander, 2002; 453 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - In the Country of my Imagination, 2002; 452 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - In the Country of My Imagination Planning, 169245 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Is Charlie Chan Really Dead?: Asians in America Conference, 1999; 451 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Kip Fulbeck Exhibition, 169247 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Maya Lin and Michael Brenson Dialogue, 1998; 450 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Maya Lin at the A/P/A Gallery, Undated; 449 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Mind's Desire by Jaishri Abichandani, 2002; 446 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Miscellaneous, 1998-2007; 222163 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Momotaro/ Peach Boy: New Works by Tomie Arai, 1998; 445 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Museum of Absences/Oveleaf Hong Kong Book Party, 169250 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - My Country Versus Me Book Launch, 2002; 444 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - My Country Versus Me Planning, 169248 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - New York Before Chinatown Book Party, 1999; 443 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Nikkei Community Symposium, 2006; 181209 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Nikkei Community Symposium, 2006; 181210 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Nikkei Community Symposium, 2006; 181211 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Nori Morimoto Exhibit, 2000; 442 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Open House Reception, 1997-2003; 440 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Pacific Islands, Atlantic Worlds Symposium, 2001; 439 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Palates of Pleasure: The Philosophy and Politics of Southeast Asian Food Symposium, 2001; 438 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Palates of Pleasure Fundraising, 2001; 181214 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Palates of Pleasure Brochures, 2001; 181215 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - A Photographic Journey with Corky Lee, 2002; 503 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Please Do Not Throw Peanuts at My God: Installation by Siddhartha Joag, 2002; 436 (Box 10, Folder 13)